(Leonard:)-Kites ho!
-Kites ho!
(Leonard:)Kites ho!
[IN UNISON]
Kites ho!
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
You're misusing the word "ho."
(Sheldon:)It's an interjection used to call attention
to a destination, not an object.
As in, uh, "Land ho!"
or, uh, "Westward ho!"
[IN UNISON]
Kites ho!
Hey, guys. What are you doing?
(Penny:)Going out to discover electricity?
[CHUCKLES]
If you refer to the work of Benjamin
Franklin, he did not discover electricity.
(Leonard:)He merely used a kite to determine
that lightning consists of electricity.
(Leonard:)He also invented the Franklin stove,
bifocals and the flexible urinary catheter.
(Leonard:)-Kites ho.
-We're heading out for some kite fighting.
(Penny:)-Kite fighting?
-Oh, yeah.
(Leonard:)It's an extremely competitive,
cutthroat sport.
(Sheldon:)Well, actually,
the risk of throat-cutting is very low.
(Sheldon:)On the other hand, severe string burn
is a real and ever-present danger.
-Uh, you wanna come watch?
-Oh, gee, ha, sounds amazing.
(Penny:)But, um, I've got some friends
coming over.
(Penny:)We're just gonna watch
the Nebraska game.
(Leonard:)Oh, football, sure.
(Howard:)Good guess.
(Penny:)I would've invited you,
but you're not a fan.
(Leonard:)No. No, I'm not. So, great.
(Leonard:)You've got plans
doing something you like...
(Leonard:)...I've got plans doing something I like,
so it's good.
(Penny:)Maybe we'll hang out
after everybody's gone.
(Leonard:)-Yeah, great.
-See you.
(Leonard:)Well, this sucks.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, I got bored and drifted off.
(Sheldon:)Where exactly in the interaction
did the sucking lie?
Leonard realized Penny's hiding him
from her friends...
(Raj:)...because he's a tiny little man
who flies kites.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that certainly would suck.